export const data = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What is first letter of English alphabets",
        options: {
            a: "A",
            b: "B",
            c: "C",
            d: "D"
        },
        correctOption: "A"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What is second letter of English alphabets",
        options: {
            a: "A",
            b: "B",
            c: "C",
            d: "D"
        },
        correctOption: "B"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "What is third letter of English alphabets",
        options: {
            a: "A",
            b: "B",
            c: "C",
            d: "D"
        },
        correctOption: "C"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What is fourth letter of English alphabets",
        options: {
            a: "A",
            b: "B",
            c: "C",
            d: "D"
        },
        correctOption: "D"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "What is fifth letter of English alphabets",
        options: {
            a: "E",
            b: "B",
            c: "C",
            d: "D"
        },
        correctOption: "A"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "What is sixth letter of English alphabets",
        options: {
            a: "E",
            b: "F",
            c: "C",
            d: "D"
        },
        correctOption: "B"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "What is seventh letter of English alphabets",
        options: {
            a: "E",
            b: "B",
            c: "G",
            d: "D"
        },
        correctOption: "C"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "What is eighth letter of English alphabets",
        options: {
            a: "H",
            b: "B",
            c: "C",
            d: "D"
        },
        correctOption: "A"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "What is ninth letter of English alphabets",
        options: {
            a: "I",
            b: "B",
            c: "C",
            d: "D"
        },
        correctOption: "A"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "What is tenth letter of English alphabets",
        options: {
            a: "J",
            b: "B",
            c: "C",
            d: "D"
        },
        correctOption: "A"
    },
]